megafounder.com 2014-08-12

# Megafounder - Privacy Policy

We ask that you take a moment to read this Privacy Policy. We want to be sure you are aware of the terms and agree with them before using our services.

This website is operated by Megafounder S. L (“Megafounder”) and this document contains the privacy terms for www.megafounder.com and any other service operated by Megafounder or redirected to this website (“the service”).

Megafounder realizes that your privacy is very important to you and we take the responsibility of protecting that data very seriously. By accepting these terms you are giving us your consent to collect and use your personal details, always in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Megafounder reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy without notification. It is always our intention to announce any changes made, but we do ask that you review the policy from time to time to ensure that you remain in agreement with the terms. By using Megafounder, you are agreeing that you accept the terms, in their entirety, as stated at that moment.

**Data Collection.**

In agreement with Spanish Organic Law 15/1999, of 13th December, governing the Protection of Personal Data, all data that you provide to us will be stored on a file, which is the sole property of Megafounder. This file is registered at the Spanish Agency for Data Protection that guarantees the security and privacy of your data.

**Megafounder collects and processes the following information:**

  * Personal details: name, email, address, country, profiles in social networks, etc.
  * Log-in information: username and password.
  * Transactional details or information required to complete a transaction.
  * Requested information regarding the service or its content: confirmations, information requests, newsletters, invitations, etc.
  * Information you provide to us regarding the service: Comments, contributions, suggestions or requests for assistance.

We ask that you use the most recent information regarding your personal data and promptly update your profile if it should change. We also ask that you only use your true identity; misrepresentation will result in disciplinary action. You are welcome to use a username or handle for our services, should you wish to keep your identity private, but we ask that you do not falsify information provided to us. Should you provide false, incomplete or inaccurate data, you are solely responsible for any consequence of the error.

If you would like to make any changes to your account, cancel your account or express your opinion regarding this policy, feel free to email us at [hello@megafounder.com](mailto:hello@megafounder.com)

**Use of your personal data.**

**We will use the information you provide us to:**

  * Identify you when you log into your account.
  * Provide you with Megafounder services.
  * Send you information you’ve requested or that could be of interest to you.
  * Administer your account in Megafounder.
  * Contact you with questions regarding your service.
  * Analyze the use of the service to improve our contents and services.

The user does have the option to store their credit card for convenience should they wish to do so. In that case, only the last four digits of the card number will be displayed. Your card information is stored securely and privately through Stripe and Project Managers do not have access to your credit card information. Stripe does allow access to the type of card used and the last four digits of the card number, which can be viewed from the Project Manager dashboard.

**Communication: email.**

Our primary form of contact is through email. We reserve the right to send you an email to confirm transactions with Megafounder or in other situations where communication with your is required to fulfill the Terms of Service.

Occasionally, we may also send emails regarding promotional information, changes in service or other helpful content. You have the option to stop receiving such emails should you request it. We have no intention of flooding your inbox.

**Third party services.**

Your privacy is important to us. Megafounder will never post on your behalf to any social network or third-party site without your permission. We also will not share your name or any other personal details with any third party unless required for the effective use of the service (for instance, sharing transaction details with Stripe.)

**Cookies.**

Cookies are small bits of information that are sent to your computer when you visit a website and which store information about your use of the service. Megafounder uses cookies to help recognize you as a repeat visitor, to improve the quality of our service and to adapt the information to your needs. The cookies used on this website are temporary. We will never use cookies to collect any personal information.

**How do they work?**

Every time you use Megafounder our web server sends a cookie to your computer which allows us to recognize it; this gives us information regarding how a certain computer uses our website. No personal information of any kind is gathered unless you are logged in, at which point only the information agreed on in this Privacy Policy is gathered.

While most browsers accept cookies by default, you can turn off the option or block cookies within your browser; however, because our service requires the use of cookies to effectively run, you may experience a limitation in service by disabling cookies. Nevertheless, by blocking or deleting cookies used on our Service, you may not be able to take full advantage of our service.

The following is a list of the most popular browsers, along with a link on how to enable or disable cookies in that browser:

  * Google Chrome: <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en>
  * Mozilla Firefox: <http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences>
  * Internet Explorer: <http://support.microsoft.com/kb/260971>
  * Safari: <http://support.apple.com/kb/PH11913>

**What cookies do we use?**

Megafounder uses the following types of cookies:

IP geolocation cookies: Cookies are used to determine the country where a service is requested from. This cookie is completely anonymous, and it’s only used to help adapt the content to your location.

Additionally, some services may connect with social networks such as Facebook or Twitter. When the user logs into the site using the credentials of a social network, it allows that social network to store a persistent cookie that remembers its identity and ensures that he has access to the services until it expires. The user can delete this cookie and revoke access to services through social networks by updating his preferences in that social network.

Analytical Cookies: each time a user visits the site, a tool from an external service provider (Google Analytics) generates an analytical cookie on the user's computer. This cookie is used to anonymously identify the visitor. It serves to:

  * Identify, anonymously, the users that surf the web (it identifies browsers and devices, not people) and therefore the approximate number of visitors and their trend in the time.
  * Identify, anonymously, the most visited content.
  * Know if the user is a new or recurring visitor.

**Voluntary Disclosure.**

Any personal information or content that you post on public areas of the service will be publicly available and Megafounder is not responsible for how the information is used after being posted. As a result, we ask you to be careful with the information you post publicly.

Project Managers may have access to personal details as names, emails or delivery addresses when necessary to provide the service.

**Other Terms.**

Megafounder does reserve the right to provide your personal information to legal entities should it be requested and required by law, or if necessary to protect our rights.

If you wish to amend or cancel the personal information you’ve provided us, just log into your account and update your profile. Some information may have to remain stored to comply with legal requirements.

We ask participants to be eighteen years or older in order to use any part of Megafounder. As a result, there are no special terms for persons under the age of eighteen.

While we take every precaution to protect your information and privacy, because of the international nature of Megafounder, it is possible the information may be transferred between countries (such as that used for Google Analytics, or if your computer should be in a different country than our server.)

**Contact.**

If you have any questions feel free to contact us at [hello@megafounder.com.](mailto:hello@megafounder.com) or by phone at +34 634 660 515 (Monday to Friday, 9am-9pm CET).

**Corporate Information.**

Megafounder S.L. is a corporation located in Girona (Spain), with registered address at 91 Emili Grahit, Monturiol building p3-b02, Parc UdG, P.C.: 17003.

Megafounder is duly registered on the Trade Registry of Girona (Spain), Volume 2898, Book 0, Sheet 53, Section 8, Sheet 53748 and its tax identification code is (ES)B55151799.

**Updated: February 2014.**
